(Leonard:)- What the hell?
- Emergency-preparedness drill.
- Oh, no. Come on.
- Yeah, you know how it works.
(Sheldon:)Once a quarter, keep our readiness up.
(Sheldon:)Now, rise and shine, sleepy head.
HaIf the town is probably dead.
(Leonard:)I have to get a lock for my door.
(Sheldon:)I think you'll like the drill tonight.
I've tried to make it fun.
(Sheldon:)Each of these cards contains a detailed
scenario of a possible apocalyptic event.
Everything from wildfires
to a surprise invasion by Canada.
(Sheldon:)Pick a catastrophe, any catastrophe.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, Canada is not
going to invade California.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, really? You think those hippies
in washington and Oregon can stop them?
Oh. Fine.